<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Passbolt Pro Edition Release notes</title>
<link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro.rss</link>
<description>Most recent release notes.</description>
<language>en-us</language>


<item>
    <title>v2.14.0 | Sunshine</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2140-sunshine</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2140-sunshine</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release. It ships with a some bug fixes and improvements for the server, mainly performance improvements for activity logs and better feedback for LDAP error messages. Changelog API [2.14.0] 2020-08-25 Added Add an option to the migrate shell task to avoid clearing the cache after the...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.13.5 | Stomp (Remix)</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2135-stomp</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2135-stomp</guid>
    <description>This is a small maintenance release. It ships with a few bug fixes and improvements for the web extension. Changelog API [2.13.5] 2019-07-29 Fixed Fix display a validation error when db password contains a quote or db name contain a dash Fix email notification settings bootstrap messes up non persistent...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.13.1 | Stomp</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2131-stomp</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2131-stomp</guid>
    <description>This is a small maintenance release. It ships with performance improvements and fixes a bug introduced with the latest release. Thank you to everyone who helped us test and iron out the last kinks! In other news, we just published an article on the blog to explain why passbolt requires...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.13.0 | Hammer to Fall</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2130-hammer-to-fall</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2130-hammer-to-fall</guid>
    <description>We just published an article on the blog to give a quick overview of this new ‘Folders’ feature. Discover the 'Folders' feature The team is pleased to announce that the much awaited “Folders” feature is available to Passbolt Pro and Passbolt Cloud subscribers as part of this release. Most of...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 18:55:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.13.0-RC1 | In The Air Tonight</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2130-in-the-air-tonight</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2130-in-the-air-tonight</guid>
    <description>The team is pleased to announce that the much awaited folders feature is available for testing as part of this release candidate. The goal of folders is to provide a tool for passbolt users to easily organize passwords. The users will be able to use nested folders (or directories), in...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 16:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.12.1 | Never Gonna Give You Up</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2121-never-gonna-give-you-up</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2121-never-gonna-give-you-up</guid>
    <description>This release contains a security fix, please update your server as soon as possible. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version. Read the doc This is a small maintenance release in order to update to jQuery v3.5. The library released an important security...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 18:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>







<item>
    <title>v2.12.0 | Call Me</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2120-call-me</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2120-call-me</guid>
    <description>This release is mainly a maintenance release. It ships with several fixes, mainly regarding the web extension. The previously published extension version contained some security fix for an issue in the quick access suggestion system reported by security researcher Rene Kroka. You can learn more about it on the incident...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 11:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.11.0 | Don't You (Forget about me)</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2110-dont-you</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2110-dont-you</guid>
    <description>Passbolt v2.11 is maintenance release containing security fixes. Extension update will be rolled out automatically to your users like usual, but as an administrator you will need to update your server. This release introduces some security fixes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 08:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.10.0 | Owner of a Lonely Heart</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2100-owner-of-a-lonely-heart</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v2100-owner-of-a-lonely-heart</guid>
    <description>This release ships with some nice improvements on the LDAP connector, administration interface and quick access features. The Ldap connector configuration UI and mapping rules have been revamped to provide a better experience, mainly for OpenLdap and FreeIPA users. The connector should now be compatible with most cases and configurations....</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.9.0 | Paint it black</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v290-paint-it-black</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v290-paint-it-black</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some security fixes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version as soon as possible. Update documentation This release introduces the ability to create entries directly from the quickaccess menu, in the browser toolbar. fig. Creating an entry from quickaccess It...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.8.4 | Where is my mind</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v284-where-is-my-mind</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v284-where-is-my-mind</guid>
    <description>This release is mainly a maintenance release. It ships with more performance improvements and fixes a few bugs reported by the community. The API has also now been fully documented. It is in 2 parts: the API documentation which is available on our help website, and the API reference which...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.8.3 | Blue Monday</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v283-blue-monday</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v283-blue-monday</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some new dependencies and database changes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version. Read the doc This new release of Passbolt Pro Edition ships with “passwords activity”, which takes care of providing the activity history corresponding to a password. With...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.7.2 | Welcome To The Jungle</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v272-welcome-to-the-jungle</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v272-welcome-to-the-jungle</guid>
    <description>This release contains two fixes, regressions shipped with v2.7.0.


  PASSBOLT-3417: LDAP: fix regression “settings cannot be saved through the UI”.
  PASSBOLT-3416: Fix the uses of php short tags in the webinstaller template files

</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.7.0 | Jump</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v270-jump</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v270-jump</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some security fixes, new dependencies and database changes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version as soon as possible. Update documentation The main focus of this release was to improve the performance and reactivity of the application, as well as...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.6.1 | Stairway to Heaven</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v261-stairway-to-heaven</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v261-stairway-to-heaven</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release that fixes some issues introduced by the previous release. It also gives more flexibility during the installation to skip providing some email settings. A big thank you to Julius Haake, Alain Devarieux and Nate Curry for reporting these issues. Passbolt API (Pro Edition) Improved PASSBOLT-3273:...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.6.0 | Start Me Up</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v260-start-me-up</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v260-start-me-up</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some new dependencies and database changes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version. Read the doc This new release of Passbolt Pro Edition introduces a new workspace for administrators. In this workspace it is now possible for an admin to...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.5.1 | Thunderstruck</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v251-thunderstruck</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v251-thunderstruck</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some new dependencies and database changes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version. Read the doc This new release of Passbolt Pro Edition introduces new multi factor authentication providers: Yubikey and Duo. These functionality relies on third party services to...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.4.0 | Final Countdown</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v240-final-countdown</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v240-final-countdown</guid>
    <description>This release introduces some new dependencies and database changes. Make sure you follow the minor update documentation to roll out this new version. Read the doc This release introduce the ability for users to select multiple passwords and perform a bulk action such as delete or share. This was a...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 13:11:11 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.3.0 | Shine On You Crazy Diamond</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v230-shine-on-you-crazy-diamond</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v230-shine-on-you-crazy-diamond</guid>
    <description>We are happy to announce the availability of passbolt directory synchronization feature. With this feature you can add and remove groups and users directly from your OpenLDAP or Active Directory and the changes will be reflected in passbolt. It is currently available as an experimental plugin for Passbolt Pro Edition...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.2.0 | I want to break free</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v220-i-want-to-break-free</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v220-i-want-to-break-free</guid>
    <description>Please note that Passbolt API V1.x will be officially unmaintained from 1st of September 2018. If you haven’t upgraded to V2.x yet, it is strongly advised to do it now since the next versions of the browser extension will not be compatible anymore with V1.x branch. This release is mainly...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.1.1 | Loungin</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v211-loungin</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v211-loungin</guid>
    <description>fig. Passbolt night mode This release introduces a new dark theme that you can use in the place of the black on white default theme. The goal for this theme was to be easier on the eye for people who stare at the screen for a long period of time...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.0.9 | Cold Vein</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v209-cold-vein</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v209-cold-vein</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release for passbolt web extension that fixes issues reported by the community. Web Extension Bug fixes Fix content scripts should not be inserted if they are already present. Fix auth pagemod should insert script when a redirection is set in url Fix json.headers should be json.header...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.0.8 | They Reminisce</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v208-untitled</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v208-untitled</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release for passbolt web extension that fixes issues reported by the community.

Web Extension
Bug fixes

  Fix backward compatibility issue with search user API v1.


</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>



<item>
    <title>v2.0.7 | Struggle</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v207-struggle</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v207-struggle</guid>
    <description>Security notice: Nginx user, please review your configuration file to make sure you are using the correct application root. It should be: /var/www/passbolt/webroot Read more This release fixes issues introduced by the v2.0.5 both in the webextension and in the API. As you can see version v2.0.6 is skipped in...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>









<item>
    <title>v2.0.5 | Everyday struggle</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v205-everydaystruggle</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v205-everydaystruggle</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance for both Passbolt Pro and Community edition. It fixes issues reported by the community such as the vulnerability reported by Matthias vd Meent, considering the use of an unsecure pseudo random number generator when generating passwords. You can learn more about the issue on the dedicated...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.0.4 | Something we all adore</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v204-somethingwealladore</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v204-somethingwealladore</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release that fixes issues reported by the community.

Passbolt API
Fixed

  COMMUNITY-599: Make email MX validation optional and not enabled by default
  GITHUB-247: Fix secrets are not deleted when deleting a group or a user


</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.0.3 | Definition</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v203-definition</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v203-definition</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release that improves compatibility with CentOS 7.

Passbolt API
Fixed

  PASSBOLT-2849: Fix issue with the permissions query and MariaDB 5.5
  PASSBOLT-2848: Fix unsafe mode and ssl offloading


</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.0.2 | Mass Appeal</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v202-mass-appeal</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v202-mass-appeal</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release that fixes a bug related to the v1 database migration. Thanks to @shochdoerfer for his contribution. Passbolt API Improved GITHUB-242: Add Auto-Submitted header to the email notifications Fixed PASSBOLT-2806: Force database columns charset and collation PASSBOLT-2781: Increase length of resource uri field in model validation...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>





<item>
    <title>v2.0.1 | Knock You Out</title>
    <link>https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v201-knock-you-out</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://help.passbolt.com/releases/pro/v201-knock-you-out</guid>
    <description>This is a maintenance release that fixes a regression introduced in v2.0.0. Many thanks to @odyx for his blazing fast reaction at reporting the bug and submitting a fix. Passbolt API Improved PASSBOLT-2511: Improve healthcheck tables list so that tables are listed per major version Fixed GITHUB-239: Fix unsafe mode...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
</item>


























</channel>
</rss>
